我们有了测试数据之后怎么让它显示到ListView视图上呢
Given some sample data how do we populate a ListView?
我们来用一套联系人的测试数据来看看它们如何显示到列表里
Let's look at an example of some contact data and how it can be displayed in
我们来看看我们这三个联系人的原始数据
the list. We start with our raw data of contacts which is three contacts,
三个人的名字和他们的头像照片  然后我们就把这些数据通过Adapter适配器初始化
as well as our profile images. Then we pass this data into the adapter so
随后我们就可以调用它了  Adapter适配器知道如何为这些数据条目生成
it has a reference to it. The adapter also knows how to build a list item layout
合适的布局元素  所以它就可以为这些数据创建布局元素了
for each of these data items. So, it could go ahead and create the layouts for
直到ListView视图需要的时候  我们才会把这些数据呈现给它
them. But we don't need to create the views yet until the ListView requests that
例如  你有上百号联系人
it needs them. For example, if you had hundreds of contacts here,
你并不需要为用不到的人搞那么多座位在你身旁
you wouldn't want hundreds of layouts sitting around that aren't being used.
然后把Adapter适配器绑定到ListView视图之后
Then when you bind the adapter to the ListView,
ListView视图会自己决定要多少个条目的
the ListView will ask how many items are actually in the data set.
因此这个Adapter适配器就会检查一下数据源  这里有三条数据
And the adapter will check in the data set there's three items, so
然后把三条数据告诉ListView视图 ListView视图就知道了他总共
we will return that to the ListView. Now the ListView knows that it will have to
要呈现三条数据  现在ListView视图会从零位开始
populate itself with three list items. Now the ListView starts at position
去找在第零位元素的布局信息
zero and asks for the list item layout located at that position. It goes back to
随之它去向Adapter适配器找第0位的数据信息  我们找到了
the adapter and the adapter checks that at position zero, we have the contact,
是Anna这个联系人  Adapter适配器知道如何如何为Anna创建一个列表元素布局
Anna. The adapter knows how to create a list item layout from the contact, Anna.
所以它就这么做了  然后就会把内容返回到LisView视图去
So, it goes ahead and does that. And then we return it to the ListView. And now
现在我们就看到了Anna这个列表项就在这个列表里的第零位
we see that the Anna list item is located at the zeroth position in the list.
随后ListView视图会去检查在第一个条目位置的内容
Next the ListView wants to get the item at position one, so
去找Adapter适配器要布局信息  然后它检查了一下第一个位置的内容
ask for the layout from the adapter. The adapter checks that at position one,
我们找到了Bob这个联系人  Adapter适配器知道如何如何为Bob创建一个列表元素布局
we have the contact Bob. The adapter knows how to create a list item layout for
所以它就这么做了  然后就会把内容返回到LisView视图去
Bob so it goes ahead and does that and then it returns it to the ListView. And
现在我们看到列表项Bob已经成功的添加到了ListView视图里了
now we see that the list item for Bob has been successfully added
它在第一个位置  然后ListView视图去得到最后一个条目
to the ListView at position one. Now, the ListView fetches its
因为它知道整个列表里总共只有三个条目
last item because it knows that there was three list items to expect.
它请求Adapter适配器  获取到第二个位置的条目布局信息
It fetches the last list item layout at position two by asking the adapter.
Adapter适配器就去检查了第二个位置的内容  找到了Charlie  包含她的头像一起
The adapter checks that at position two, we have Charlie, as well as that image.
然后Adapter适配器知道如何如何为Charlie创建一个列表元素布局
And we know how to make a list item layout for Charlie, so we can go ahead and
返回给ListView视图之后  Charlie这个联系人条目也就显示到ListView视图里了
do that, and return it to the ListView. And now we have the list item for
现在 我们已经完成了我们这个列表啦
Charlie and position two in the list. And we have our complete list